<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kubernetes on T-Mobile Open Source</title>
    <link>/tags/kubernetes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kubernetes on T-Mobile Open Source</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 10:51:21 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/kubernetes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The [Machine] Learning is Never Done</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/hanson-ml-retraining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 10:51:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/hanson-ml-retraining/</guid>
      <description>You’ve built a model that stakeholders love. Now, you need it to retrain every day… and that requires a whole new architecture.
In this article, Mark Eric Hanson outlines why automated ML model retraining is important, the use cases it solves for T-Mobile, and how to stitch the tech together to recreate a similar implementation of your own. Its a fascinating read, and a good behind-the-scenes look at how we approach problem-solving at T-Mobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Out the Magenta Tape: Policy-as-Code for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/rolling-out-the-magenta-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 01:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/rolling-out-the-magenta-tape/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, I&amp;rsquo;m Joe Searcy, Member of Technical Staff on the Platform Engineering team here at T-Mobile and I&amp;rsquo;m joined by Torin Sandall, Software Engineer at Styra and Co-founder/Core Contributor for the Open Policy Agent (OPA) project, to help tell the story behind one of T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s latest open source projects, MagTape.
History &amp;amp; Motivation Here at T-Mobile we&amp;rsquo;re ALL-IN on containers and container platforms like Kubernetes. We, like most companies building Kubernetes environments, came to a quick realization that empowering your developers with platforms like Kubernetes can exponentially increase the volume and velocity of applications and releases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conducktor-Go for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/conducktor-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/conducktor-go/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes (R) has become the Container orchestration platform of choice&amp;ndash;but launching and configuring a Production grade Kubernetes Cluster is a lot of work. Conducktor-Go simplifies launching native Kubernetes Clusters on AWS (R) using Terraform (TM), Ansible (R), and Python Scripts. It also provides a rich, turn-key telemetry solution with pre-configured Grafana(R) dashboards and Prometheus(R) as data source.
Conducktor-GO also configures Nginx(R), Docker(R) CE, Weave Net (CNI), Kube2IAM, Kubernetes 2.0 Dashboard, Kube-State-Metrics, and Metrics Server to provide a Production ready Kubernetes Cluster to deploy your services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
