<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>oss on T-Mobile Open Source</title>
    <link>/tags/oss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in oss on T-Mobile Open Source</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 01:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/oss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Out the Magenta Tape: Policy-as-Code for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/rolling-out-the-magenta-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 01:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/rolling-out-the-magenta-tape/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, I&amp;rsquo;m Joe Searcy, Member of Technical Staff on the Platform Engineering team here at T-Mobile and I&amp;rsquo;m joined by Torin Sandall, Software Engineer at Styra and Co-founder/Core Contributor for the Open Policy Agent (OPA) project, to help tell the story behind one of T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s latest open source projects, MagTape.
History &amp;amp; Motivation Here at T-Mobile we&amp;rsquo;re ALL-IN on containers and container platforms like Kubernetes. We, like most companies building Kubernetes environments, came to a quick realization that empowering your developers with platforms like Kubernetes can exponentially increase the volume and velocity of applications and releases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Lean Mean Pipeline Machine</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/a-lean-mean-pipeline-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/a-lean-mean-pipeline-machine/</guid>
      <description>Keeping in mind the dynamic DevOps culture in our company and others, we set out to streamline our development pipelines using a modern container-based approach. Our goal was to empower developers to have the flexibility and ease of adapting the pipeline to their development methodologies while providing more time for development and testing rather than spending time on creating and maintaining CI/CD pipelines.
Developers can easily on-board their solutions without spending too much time learning about the underlying technology that drives the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Kardio</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/introducing-kardio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 13:19:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/introducing-kardio/</guid>
      <description>Containers, Kubernetes and Health Checks for the Win! With the massive adoption of containers, many large enterprises as well as startups embracing containers in their application architecture patterns. With this huge growth, we have new challenges to monitor 1000’s of containers running in 10’s and 100’s of Container Platforms such as Kubernetes.
There are many APM (Application Performance Management) products that provide end to end monitoring of application services. However, it can be complicated to build dashboards to get simple status of these services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monarch: App-level Chaos Engineering</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/monarch-app-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/monarch-app-level/</guid>
      <description>Motivation As we have talked about in an earlier post, Chaos Engineering is a method by which the stability of complicated cloud infrastructures can be assessed and validated. The current Chaos Engineering tools do not support application-specific attacks, but rather vm-specific attacks. Now, this works if each application is on its own VM, but a lot of our applications are deployed in Cloud Foundry which moves apps without the developers even needing to know what VM their container is running on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Codeless: T-Mobile’s Take on Test Automation Frameworks</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/introducing-codeless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/introducing-codeless/</guid>
      <description>Reliable, maintainable test automation, delivered by anyone.
Continuous Delivery drives towards faster time to market which in turns demands new code to be tested and verified at high speed. For many years, QA and development teams have leveraged test automation tools to allow more tests to be run in a shorter amount of time. However, some teams may not have enough runway to build test automation &amp;ldquo;SDET&amp;rdquo; skillsets to meet demanding release timeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I created my first open source node module?</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/orchestration-desk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/orchestration-desk/</guid>
      <description>Why I wrote Orchestration Desk? Hello everybody !! I will be writing my first tech blog today. The topic I will be covering is &amp;ldquo;why I wrote a open source module &amp;lsquo;Orchestration-Desk&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo; (https://github.com/tmobile/orchestration-desk/wiki) along with one of my favorite topic &amp;ldquo;Feature Toggles&amp;rdquo;. Feature toggles are very popular among software industry /teams that wants continuous development and release of software products. The teams want the ability to show/hide features on demand. I believe any team can create their own little feature toggles system using some of the popular tools available to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pi Alarm</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/pi-alarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/pi-alarm/</guid>
      <description>Purpose: To control an alarm using a Raspberry Pi and Python At T-Mobile, our development teams run pipelines to build, test, and deploy our code. Any disruption in the pipeline means new code can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered, so fixing pipeline issues when they arise becomes top priority. To emphasize the importance of having an &amp;ldquo;always on&amp;rdquo; pipeline, we wanted a way to alert the teams explicitly, rather than just notifications via email/chat, when there&amp;rsquo;s a failure in the job pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing PacBot</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/introducing-pacbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/introducing-pacbot/</guid>
      <description>Gartner predicts that &amp;ldquo;through 2020, 95 percent of cloud security failures will be the customer&amp;rsquo;s fault.&amp;rdquo; The very nature of public cloud, the ease at which developers can create, modify and delete resources &amp;ndash;gives us the agility we love but also makes it easy to overlook security guidelines. The dynamic nature of the cloud further complicates matters, especially if you have a very large footprint.
From a recent survey conducted by cybersecurity-insiders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile and Open Source: A Look Back on Year One</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/tmobile-oss-lookback/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/tmobile-oss-lookback/</guid>
      <description>It was one year ago today (on my birthday) that T-Mobile publicly embraced the open source community with the release of Jazz — a framework to unlock the full potential of serverless computing. It was both the start of a new journey for T-Mobile and a significant milestone along a path that we have been on for the past two and a half years: from telco to technology company.
So, I think now is a great time to reflect on the progress we made over the last year…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Start of Chaos Engineering at T-Mobile</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/chaos-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:10:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/chaos-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Overview At T-Mobile, we have been making a large push toward cloud infrastructures. Through this process, we have been taking large monoliths from the past and breaking them into a series of microservices. This allows us to easily scale parts of services which are overloaded with requests and to increase the redundancy of our systems by having backups ready to go in the event one of them crashes or the hosting hardware has issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Project Casquatch</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/casquatch-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/casquatch-intro/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Project Casquatch At T-Mobile, we have been rapidly developing new applications on top of a micro-service architecture through a combination of Java and Cassandra, including all the latest and greatest technologies. This is great except that Cassandra pushes a significant amount of the performance tuning and high availability configuration from the database layer up to the application layer. This leads to a few problems for the enterpise as all these policies are individually implemented (or not) by each service and database availability is now out of central control, leaving each developer to implement as they see fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile @ SpringOne platform conference</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/tmo-at-s1p/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/tmo-at-s1p/</guid>
      <description>SpringOne platform is a premier conference that brings leading software companies, enterprises and cloud architects who build and run cloud native applications to share and collaborate their experiences. You can catch engineers from T-Mobile at SpringOne. We also have two talks, you can find links to those talks below. If you are at SpringOne come check us out and say hello. Hope to see you there.
Tuesday 2:00p-3:00p PST (60 min) at Room: 2010 Zero to 12 Million</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catch T-Mobile @ re:Invent!</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/re-invent-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/re-invent-blog/</guid>
      <description>T-Mobile is transforming wireless, and the public cloud is a key enabler of that transformation. This week, technologists from around the world are gathering in Las Vegas for re:Invent, a conference for Amazon Web Services and the public cloud.
As one of the largest tech events of the year, it&amp;rsquo;s a great venue for the Un-carrier to showcase the innovative development work we are doing. Here are the great stories being presented by T-Mobilers this week&amp;ndash;be sure to check out the webcasts!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile embraces open source</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/t-mobile-embraces-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/t-mobile-embraces-open-source/</guid>
      <description>As the Un-carrier, T-Mobile is transforming wireless. Technology and software development play a key role in enabling that transformation.
We work every day on technology to make systems more robust while enabling faster delivery at reduced cost&amp;ndash;all so we can provide more value to our customers!
Today we are making available as open source, both large and small projects that contribute to that effort:
 Jazz  Jazz is being developed by T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Center of Excellence to make it easier to develop, deploy and operate solutions, shifting workloads from VMs and IaaS to serverless and container platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conducktor-Go for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/conducktor-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/conducktor-go/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes (R) has become the Container orchestration platform of choice&amp;ndash;but launching and configuring a Production grade Kubernetes Cluster is a lot of work. Conducktor-Go simplifies launching native Kubernetes Clusters on AWS (R) using Terraform (TM), Ansible (R), and Python Scripts. It also provides a rich, turn-key telemetry solution with pre-configured Grafana(R) dashboards and Prometheus(R) as data source.
Conducktor-GO also configures Nginx(R), Docker(R) CE, Weave Net (CNI), Kube2IAM, Kubernetes 2.0 Dashboard, Kube-State-Metrics, and Metrics Server to provide a Production ready Kubernetes Cluster to deploy your services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
